export const historyQuiz = {
    totalQuestions: 5,
    questions: [
      {
        id: 1,
        question: 'During what period did the title of Dictator originate?',
        options: ['Roman Republic', 'Napoleonic Europe', 'Soviet Union'],
        correctAnswer: 'Roman Republic',
      },
      {
        id: 2,
        question: 'Where did Joseph Stalin, Winston Churchill and Franklin D. Roosevelt meet following the conclusion of WW2?',
        options: ['Yalta', 'Dunkirk', 'Pearl Harbor'],
        correctAnswer: 'Yalta',
      },
      {
        id: 3,
        question: 'When did the Berlin Wall fall?',
        options: ['1988', '1989', '1987'],
        correctAnswer: '1989',
      },
    ],
  };
  

  export const generalKnowledgeQuiz = {
    totalQuestions: 5,
    questions: [
      {
        id: 1,
        question: 'What is the name of the weak zone of the earth\'s crust?',
        options: ['Seismic', 'Cosmic', 'Anaemic'],
        correctAnswer: 'Seismic',
      },
      {
        id: 2,
        question: 'The worldâ€™s nation 5G mobile network was launched by which country?',
        options: ['Malaysia', 'USA', 'South Korea'],
        correctAnswer: 'South Korea',
      },
      {
        id: 3,
        question: 'The green planet in the solar system is?',
        options: ['Mars', 'Earth', 'Uranus'],
        correctAnswer: 'Uranus',
      },
    ],
  };
  


  export const geographyQuiz = {
    totalQuestions: 5,
    questions: [
      {
        id: 1,
        question: 'During what period did the title of Dictator originate?',
        options: ['Roman Republic', 'Napoleonic Europe', 'Soviet Union'],
        correctAnswer: 'Roman Republic',
      },
      {
        id: 2,
        question: 'Where did Joseph Stalin, Winston Churchill and Franklin D. Roosevelt meet following the conclusion of WW2?',
        options: ['Yalta', 'Dunkirk', 'Pearl Harbor'],
        correctAnswer: 'Yalta',
      },
      {
        id: 3,
        question: 'When did the Berlin Wall fall?',
        options: ['1988', '1989', '1987'],
        correctAnswer: '1989',
      },
    ],
  };
  


  export const sportsQuiz = {
    totalQuestions: 5,
    questions: [
      {
        id: 1,
        question: 'Ryder cup is related to which sports?',
        options: ['Tennis', 'Golf', 'Formula F1'],
        correctAnswer: 'Golf',
      },
      {
        id: 2,
        question: 'Which is the only Grand Slam tournament to use Clay Court?',
        options: ['US Open', 'Australian Open', 'French Open'],
        correctAnswer: 'French Open',
      },
      {
        id: 3,
        question: 'Which of the following is known as an off-stump?',
        options: ['The stump on the same side as batsman\'s legs', 'The stump on the side of batsman\'s bat', 'The stump on either side of the middle stump'],
        correctAnswer: 'The stump on the side of batsman\'s bat',
      },
    ],
  };
  